Now, hand me that thing. - This?
No, no. LEANNE: This?
- Dad.
- Wait.
Dad, you have asked for
every tool known to man.
- You'll have to be more specific.
- Hand me the thing I had...
- This?
- No, no.
Yeah, that, that,
yeah, give me that.
Ow! Are we almost done?
I have no idea.
Dad, you know God put plumbers
- in the phone book for a reason.
- Ha, ha.
- Ow, ow!
- Come in!
- Dad. Dad.
- Come in.
- Hold that. Hold that.
- Please...
No, Dad, come right back. Oh.
Ow. Dad.
Ouch.
Dad, I can't do this.
Be right back.
Hello, Ben.
Laura.
Oh, Laura.
Aren't you grown up?
- Well, it's been 11 years.
- Ah.
Last time I saw you
was at Mom's funeral.
Oh. You live in Mt. Harlan?
No, Atlanta. I work at a clothing
store at the mall in Marietta.
I'm the assistant manager.
- Oh. LEANNE: Dad,
are you still out there?
- You ever meet my daughter?
- No, I don't think I have.
Dad?
- Oh.
- Leanne?
The blood's
draining from my arm.
That's okay. Turn that
loose. Come on out here.
- Oh, Dad.
- Leanne Mclntyre, this is Laura Miller.
I'm her godfather.
Oh, Laura Miller from Mt. Harlan,
yes, your parents owned the bakery.
I live in Atlanta now. Is
everything all right with you all?
- Yeah.
- Uh, yeah. Yeah.
Uh, Leanne was fixing the sink.
Well, I just came by to tell
you that I'm getting married.
Oh! Sit down here.
Who are you marrying?
To Paul Retzke. He
lives in Mt. Harlan too.
Remember him?
His dad was the vet.
Paul's a teacher.
He's wonderful.
- When's the wedding?
- In a couple of months.
Since my parents passed
away and we both live in Atlanta,
we decided to get married
here instead of back home.
Which brings me to why I came.
It would mean a lot to me
if you would give me away.
If you would rather not, I can
always ask my brother, Chuck.
I'd be honored.
Oh, Ben, thanks so much.
Is it gonna be a big wedding?
Between the both of us, we know
just about everybody in Mt. Harlan,
so we had to invite everyone
so no one would feel left out.
It won't be much of a reception,
I'm afraid. It's not in the budget.
Well, we can certainly chip in.
No. No, no.
- I didn't come looking for handouts.
- No handouts.
We could host an open house
the day before the wedding.
- No, no handouts.
- Dad, it's a wedding.
The wedding is the event.
We'll have it here before
the rehearsal at the church,
sort of a pre-wedding reception.
- Oh, that'd be great.
- Oh!
Thank you so much.
Thank you. Well, I have to
be going. I'll see my way out.
- Thank you both. Okay, thank you.
- Okay, we'll talk soon. Bye.
Oh, Dad, a wedding reception
right here at the house.
Doesn't that make
you feel fabulous?
Oh, Dad.
Hi.
How are you? Hi.
- Hi. Chips?
- Thanks!
And then the little guy says,
"You better watch yourself, bud."
Where did these
people come from?
Not Mars.
Ben, Ben, Ben, excuse me, Ben.
Can I talk to you for one second?
- One second?
- I gotta get out.
Practically the whole of
Mt. Harlan's here. Ha, ha.
You think Chuck will come?
Chuck? Yeah, why not?
In spite of what happened,
he's still Laura's brother.
Come on. Let's mingle. Ha, ha.
Let's go. MAN: Let's go watch.
Keep going, keep going!
Come on, man.
Time! Time! Gray has got it.
The winner and still champ.
So, what else you think
you can beat me at, Matt?
- You cheated.
- I cheated. How could I cheat?
You didn't sit up all the way.
I kicked your butt fair and
square just like I always do.
He hasn't won a sports event
since he played high school football.
The only reason he won was because
he was on a championship team.
- Ooh.
- Yeah, keep it up, Brad.
It'll make you look
all the more stupid
when I win the volunteer
fireman's competition this year.
- That's a laugh.
- No. That is a fact.
I'm gonna kick your butt then
too. It gets easier every year.
You want to know why, Matthew?
Because every year, that butt of
yours gets just a little bit bigger.
- How about a sandwich?
- Oh, thanks.
Thanks.
When does Obermeir get here?
When's she leaving?
- Where have you been?
- Outside.
Thanks! Now, that's more like it.
Those chips were kind of greasy.
Excuse me, Pop.
Ben. Ben. Ben!
Come here. I want you
to meet Ryland Hayward.
- George Hayward's boy?
- That's me.
- This is my girlfriend, Sarah Eldridge.
- Hi, it's nice to meet you.
Ry, I really need some water.
You come with me. I'll
find you something to drink.
Poor girl's practically
dying of thirst, Ben.
You're not a very good host.
This guy is really something, isn't he,
Mr. Matlock? Always on top of things.
Working with one of the most
famous lawyers in the country.
Writing briefs, arguing before
the Supreme Court. Heh.
It's a little stuffy in here.
Why don't we go outside?
- Excuse us, Ry. WOMAN:
He said that? Really? Oh.
- Oh. God, there's too many people.
- Yeah.
- I need to talk to you about something.
- I got to go to the store.
Make a list. Give me
something to write with.
Okay. It's kind of important. I've been
wanting to mention it for some time.
- Bologna. Everybody likes bologna.
- Bologna, speaking of bologna, um...
Family pack.
I may have overstated
my current employment...
- My current employment status.
- Maybe four or five packs.
- Hot dogs. A couple dozen packs.
- Some people I went to school with
- back at Mt. Harlan...
- Buns.
- Ketchup, mustard.
- I don't want to let anyone down.
I wanted people to know that even if
somebody comes from a small town,
they can make
something of themselves.
I more or less told people that I
was a full partner in your law firm.
I didn't really lie.
I didn't mean to lie. I just... One
slight misrepresentation of the facts
led to another and things
just sort of snowballed.
I don't have a partner.
Leanne ain't even a partner.
I know, and I'm sorry. And it would
never, ever happen again. Ever.
But since it has, and since it would
be embarrassing to tell everyone I lied,
couldn't you just go along with
me for one day, two days, maybe,
until everyone goes back
to Mt. Harlan? Please?
No.
Every time I come in
here, there's more people.
They're like rabbits,
they just eat and multiply.
Well, let's remember Laura
and Paul are having a good time,
- and that's all that really matters.
- All right, cookies.
You listen to me and you listen
good. You don't take the whole platter.
You take one cookie. You
got that? One cookie. One.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello, Ben.
Nice party. Must have
been Leanne's idea.
Where's he going
with those suitcases?
Him and a couple other
people couldn't find motel rooms,
- so I told them they could stay here.
- You what?
I got people staying
at my house too, Ben.
You run out of beds upstairs, let
them sleep down here on the floor.
Upstairs. Boys to the
right, girls to the left.
Everybody? Everybody who's in the
wedding needs to get to the church.
It's time for the rehearsal.
Not too fast. Slow
down. Flowers high.
That's it.
This is killing me.
We've got to talk.
All right, Laura. As soon as your
maid of honor turns around, you start.
Last time I did this, it
didn't turn out too good.
- Leanne's divorced?
- Yeah.
Married outside her species.
He was a jackass.
All right. That's very nice.
How much you gonna rake
in this year? A hundred grand?
Yeah, probably.
Probably about that much.
Why are you living in that dumpy place
instead of some nice, big ritzy condo?
Yeah. Sarah and I
could be staying with you
instead of with those two escapees
from The Love Boat up there.
You know, I haven't found a place,
um, you know, ritzy enough yet.
Speaking of The Love Boat, when
are you and Sarah going to get married?
Isn't it about time
you fished or cut bait?
Well, my job still keeps
me on the road a lot.
I figure it's kind of stupid to get married
if you're not home to enjoy the perks.
Oh.
So who is going to Paul's
bachelor party tonight?
The real question is,
who's going to be able to drive
home from Paul's bachelor party?
Ha, ha. Shh. Ahem.
- You got it, Matt.
- Come on now, Matt.
- Go, go, go!
- Push it!
I'm gonna whoop
you so bad this year,
- you'll be lucky to win the cake walk.
- Two out of three. Come on.
All right!
You'd think they would've
outgrown this by now.
Yeah, well, once a
jock, always a jock.
Chuck!
Glad you could make it.
You all remember Laura's
brother, Chuck, don't you?
- I remember him.
- Hey, hey. Brad, don't start.
Come on. You
don't have to leave.
Oh, yes, I do. Have
a beer. Enjoy yourself.
- I don't drink anymore.
- Oh, well, aren't you the saint?
- Come on, Brad.
- Too bad it's a little late.
You were drinking the night you
drove my brother into that tree.
- Take it easy, Brad.
- Have you seen him lately?
Here, I'll show you a picture.
This is him at Christmas in
his brand-new wheelchair.
I'm sorry, Brad. It
was an accident.
- One I'll regret for the rest of my life.
- You bet you will.
I'm sorry, man, I didn't
mean to wreck your party.
- I know.
- I mean, I tried to leave.
I know. Look, I left the vows in the
chapel. Sit down. Sober up, okay?
- Okay.
- Good.
Found them. Looks like
the wedding's on... again.
Morning, Mr. Matlock. I
made coffee. Hope that's okay.
Any left?
That smells good!
Morning, Ben. Oh,
good, you made coffee.
Uh, cups are right over
there. Help yourself.
Oh, good.
What are you doing here?
I brought my house
guests over for breakfast.
Why can't they
eat at your house?
I'm a retired farmer, Ben. I can't
afford to feed all these people.
What happened to all the
food? This thing was full.
You're not a very good
host. Better go to the market.
Dad. Dad. Dad.
I just came from Laura's place.
Something horrible has happened.
He punched me, and
then I tried to punch him,
and then we just went at it.
I don't know. Then I
turned around and left.
What is supposed to be a wonderful
event has just turned into a nightmare.
When you left, where'd you go?
I went to Laura's. I turned the
TV on. I fell asleep on the couch.
She there? CHUCK: No.
Her and the bridesmaids were
out someplace. Next thing I know,
she was waking me up, telling me
there's cops wanted to talk to me.
I knew Brad was
gonna be at the party.
I just wanted to see if he'd
forgive me for his brother.
His brother?
Yeah, Frank, he
was a football player.
Pro teams were starting to scout
him when he was in this car accident.
He was paralyzed from the waist
down. Chuck here was driving.
I was drunk.
Brad hated my guts.
I can't say as I blame him.
People in town get upset?
Are you kidding?
Frank was like Mt. Harlan's
greatest football player ever.
It was as if I injured
him on purpose.
I was drunk.
It was an accident.
Well, the police found
the knife that killed Brad
in back of Laura's house.
Look...
Mr. Matlock, I
didn't put it there.
I did not kill Brad. I swear.
I'll see if I can get
you out of here.
Thanks. Both of you.
I sure am glad you
two are partners.
- Hi.
It's Sarah, right?
Sarah Eldridge.
- Ry's girlfriend?
- Yeah.
You okay?
Actually, my
stomach's a little upset.
Are there any crackers
or something around here?
Sure, I just bought some.
If you wait about five minutes, I
can make some scrambled eggs.
Oh, no, I'll be lucky if I
can keep these down.
Too much to drink last night?
That and what happened to Brad.
Did you know him well?
He was a friend.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for the crackers.
Sure.
His brother-in-law
is a policeman.
Have you seen Chuck?
Yeah. He'll be out
on bail tomorrow.
Man, how could something
so awful have happened?
- I don't know.
- We've postponed the wedding.
Come on, sweetheart.
You need to eat something.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
So, uh, Mr. Matlock, did you
come up with a game plan yet?
- Game plan?
- Yeah, for defending Chuck.
Cliff told me that's the first thing you
always do, come up with a game plan.
Not yet. Excuse me.
- No she isn't.
- She is.
- She can't be.
- Why not?
Because Ry would have told me.
- Told you what?
- That Sarah's pregnant.
She is not... She has an
upset stomach, no big deal.
She said she had a hangover but
Laura said she didn't drink last night,
which was another
indication that she's pregnant.
Ry Hayward is not the type who
would keep something like this a secret.
- Maybe he didn't know about it.
- Well...
- Why wouldn't she tell him?
- Good question.
You done? Because if you
are, Cliff and I need to talk.
I'd really like to,
uh, but Detective Garrison
said he would meet me, uh,
at the hotel where Brad was
staying, so I should really go do that.
Sorry. See you later. Bye.
That's what we always talked
about when we were kids,
how we were all gonna grow
up and become volunteer firemen.
So why didn't you?
Huh. Became a lawyer.
I guess if I hadn't, I'd be
putting out fires right now.
Oh, we, uh, found a list of names
and phone numbers in his wallet.
- Oh? Did you check it out?
- Some of them.
He was hitting up
people for money.
Really? Say what
he needed it for?
Said his car broke down.
Oh, and, uh, see
this last number here?
It's a doctor's office.
Gynecologist.
How's your stomach feeling?
So-so.
How far along are you?
What makes you
think I'm pregnant?
Enough of my friends have had
babies for me to know the signs.
How come you haven't told Ry?
Maybe you're wrong.
Maybe there's nothing to tell.
I spoke to Cliff.
He said Brad was asking
everybody he knew here in Atlanta
if he could borrow money.
Seems he needed
about a thousand dollars.
Made an appointment with an
OB/GYN for someone named Sally Eller.
That's you, isn't it?
Is the baby Brad's?
Brad was murdered, Sarah.
Questions aren't going
to stop here, believe me.
I can never get everything
back in this thing.
- Ready to roll?
- Yeah.
- Is there something the matter?
- Just take me home.
Okay. Let's go say
goodbye to Laura.
Now, be sure and look
under all the furniture.
I wouldn't want you to come back
here just to pick up a toothbrush. Heh.
Uh, Ben.
Uh, excuse me, do you
remember Detective Garrison?
Oh, yeah, how are you?
- These people came for the wedding?
- Yeah.
- What are they doing?
- They're leaving.
They can't do that. Hey,
hey! Hold on a minute.
Detective Robert Garrison,
Atlanta Police Department.
I'm investigating the
murder of Bradley Thorne.
I'm afraid you'll have to stay right
here until my people ask some questions.
Uh, shouldn't take long,
just, uh, two or three days.
Four at the most.
Thanks, Deb.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
It feels good to get away
from all those people.
Yeah.
Sure does.
How'd it go with the cops?
They asked me what
I was doing that night
and I told them I was
partying with the girls.
- I can't drink this all. Have some beer.
- No, thanks.
Just one glass.
I said no.
You know,
heh, you used to
drink beer all the time.
Now you never drink it at all.
In fact, you never drink
any alcohol anymore.
- So maybe I don't want to.
- Why not?
I just want to know what's
going on with you, Sarah.
Tell me.
Nothing.
Damn it, how can you even think
of having that kid? Brad is dead!
I can count the days
as good as you can.
- And you never said anything.
- What could I say?
I was gone for a whole month,
Sarah. I knew it wasn't mine.
How did you know it was Brad's?
I saw the way he stared at you,
I saw how you looked at
him. This was no secret.
Don't do this to me, please.
Don't do this to us.
Where were you that night, Ry?
- What night?
- The night Brad was murdered.
You didn't get into bed till after
2. He was murdered around 1.
I don't believe this.
You think I had something
to do with Brad's death?
You weren't at Laura's.
It took me a while to drive back
from the bachelor party. I got lost.
Why didn't you go home with Cliff
like you said you were going to?
Look. Here are the keys.
I'll walk back to Laura's.
Morning, Ben. Want some coffee?
- Yeah.
You'll have to make another
pot. We finished this one.
What's for breakfast?
It's in the fridge.
Where?
Bottom shelf.
You'll have to do
better than this.
Are you blind, or what?
There were four dozen jelly
doughnuts in there just last night.
That explains all those little
red stains on your sofa in there.
I thought there was
another murder. Heh.
Hey. Where can I find
some clean towels?
Ooh. What are these?
Those are pictures some fella
took at Paul's bachelor party.
- How about getting me a set?
- What for?
What do you think?
- Whew.
- I might need them.
I know who killed Brad. He won the Mt.
Harlan Volunteer Fireman Competition
for four straight years.
I don't understand why
people get so excited
about climbing ladders
and dragging hoses around.
Yeah, well, to some people,
it's the high point of the year.
You know how
it is in Mt. Harlan.
Anyway, the fella who came in second
four straight years was Matt Brown.
The fella that was just in
here looking for clean towels?
Yeah. Cliff said they were always
competing against one another.
Brad spent all his time at the bachelor
party beating Matt at hand wrestling.
Cliff said he's an even worse
loser now than he was in high school,
and in high school,
he was terrible.
Ben, use your brain. Do I have
to spell everything out for you?
You're saying Matt killed Brad
because he beat him at arm wrestling?
No.
He killed him because
he wanted to be sure
he wins the fireman
competition this year.
Stranger things have
happened, you know.
I'm going to the store.
Uh, you're out of toilet paper.
Excuse me.
- Hi.
- Sir.
Uh, listen, I left something at the desk
for Brad Thorne a couple nights ago.
- Brad Thorne is dead.
- Yeah, I know.
And since he obviously never
got what I left for him, I'd like it back.
It was in a white envelope.
Okay, uh, perhaps it got put in
a file somewhere. I'll go check.
Are you still back there?
Yep. Still looking.
Detective Robert Garrison, Atlanta
police. I'd like to ask some questions.
- About what?
- The thousand dollars you left here
for Mr. Thorne the
night he was murdered.
Hey, Mr. Matlock.
- You need some help?
- Yeah, boy.
- You go for a run?
- Yeah, I did five miles.
I've been training for
the fireman competition.
Something I got to ask you.
Yeah, what's that?
Well...
Never mind.
Forget it.
- How you doing?
- Hey, Cliff, thanks for coming down.
What are friends for?
So,
tell me about the money.
Well, like I told the cops,
Brad had lent me some money,
and I was just paying him back.
The police think Brad
was blackmailing you.
He wasn't blackmailing me.
Well, he apparently
needed money badly.
He called everyone he knew, trying
to scrape together a thousand dollars.
I had a very long talk with
Sarah this morning, Ry.
A very long talk.
When I heard through a mutual
friend that Brad needed money,
I put two and two
together and figured out
that he needed it to
pay for an abortion.
So I got the money
and I left it for him at the
motel in a plain white envelope
so he wouldn't know
it came from me.
- You never confronted him?
- I just wanted everything to go away.
I thought if I didn't rock the boat,
Sarah and I could just start over,
and I could eventually make her
forget this whole thing ever happened.
Where'd you go after
the bachelor party?
Well, I heard Brad say that he was
gonna go to the church with Paul,
so I dropped the money
off at the motel and then I...
I just drove around.
I wasn't feeling real good
about myself at that point.
Mr. Hayward, we're all
done here. You can go.
Appreciate your cooperation.
Does this mean I'm
not a suspect anymore?
Why drop off money for Brad if
you were planning on killing him?
It doesn't make any sense.
- Thank you very much, detective.
- Sure.
- Come on. I'll drive you home.
- No flies on you, counselor.
I see why Ben Matlock
snapped you up.
Yeah. Come on.
Oh. Hello, Dad.
What are you writing?
- Confession.
- Confession to what?
I'm gonna kill Billy.
- You're gonna kill Billy.
- Mm-hm.
He's the one that brought people
here, eating me into the poor house.
So I'm gonna kill him.
I'll plead temporary insanity.
If the courts like
me, I'll get out in five,
maybe six years.
- Dad...
- Give yourself a raise.
You'll be working harder.
Should I make
Cliff a full partner?
It's your firm. Do
what you want to.
Come on, Dad. I'll
buy you some lunch.
Come on. Let's go.
It's well-written, isn't it?
It is really something, you being
partners with a guy like Ben Matlock.
- Uh-huh.
- You got any big cases coming up?
Yeah, probably. Uh, something's
always around the corner.
Right.
You know, I can't do this.
Do what?
Ry, I got a little problem.
- A problem with me?
- No, no, no.
I got a problem with me.
I haven't been honest with you. I
haven't been honest with anyone.
I'm not Ben's law partner.
- Ben doesn't have any partners.
- You wrote me when you...
I know, I know, I
know what I wrote.
In high school, I was never "most likely
to succeed," never lettered in any sport.
You were on the debate
team for four years.
Yes, I was, and I was
good at that. Yeah.
So I thought maybe, you
know, I'd make a good lawyer,
and maybe one day I
will make a good lawyer,
but right now, I'm
just Ben's assistant.
- His assistant, huh?
- Yeah.
Truth is, you're an assistant to the
best criminal lawyer in the country.
You have a job thousands of
law-school graduates would die to get.
Why don't you wake
up and smell the coffee?
I'll tell you something else:
You got me out of jail faster than
a jackrabbit running from a fire.
You're pretty good in my book.
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
Pizza's here.
It smells good.
Where's the
pepperoni/sausage one?
Save two pieces for me.
- Is this...?
- This looks good.
When were you gonna tell me?
I don't know.
Ry, I didn't know what to do.
It's over, you know.
Knowing it's not
mine, I just can't...
I know.
We ordered a
bunch of pizzas. Heh.
Got one just for you.
Here, it's on us.
Thanks. That's really nice.
You gotten the jelly
stains out of the couch yet?
I'm, uh, still working on it.
- So, Dad, what do you think?
- I don't know.
Hold the phone. That's it.
- What's it?
- The stain.
Which one?
When we finally got them pulled
apart, Chuck gave Brad this look,
and then he turned and
went slamming out the door.
So it appeared to you
that the defendant was angry with
Mr. Thorne when he left that night?
He just picked himself
up off the ground.
He was humiliated,
totally humiliated.
No further questions.
Uh, were...
Were you mad at Mr. Thorne when
you left the bachelor party that night?
Me? No. MATLOCK: No?
Well, I hear that you and Brad
spent most of that night arm
wrestling with one another
and you lost most
of the matches.
And you don't like to
lose, do you, Mr. Brown?
Well, nobody likes to lose.
Uh, I hear that you were in a
horseshoe competition last year.
- That's right.
- How'd you make out?
Came in second.
I understand the fella who won
had to be taken to the
hospital that day, how come?
Um...
I broke his jaw.
Because he beat you?
No, because he kept
needling me about it.
He was a poor sport.
And that made you mad?
Yeah.
Did Brad Thorne ever needle you?
- Sometimes.
- Yeah.
I know he did.
He was needling you the day of
the bachelor party. I heard him myself.
He was saying how he
was going to beat you
at the Mt. Harlan Volunteer
Fireman's Competition this year.
Didn't he?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yeah.
That competition
is a big thing in Mt. Harlan.
People talk about it for
months before and months after.
Oh, it's something big.
Did you ever win one of them?
No. MATLOCK: How come?
I don't know.
You never won one
because Brad always
beat you. Didn't he?
Yeah. I guess.
He was bragging about
it at the bachelor party.
He said he'd whooped you before
and he'd whoop you again. Right?
Yeah. MATLOCK:
How'd that make you feel?
- Well, it didn't make me very happy.
- Made you mad, didn't it?
Made you furious.
Made you want to put a
stop to it once and for all.
No.
When the bachelor
party broke up,
you followed Paul
and Brad to the church,
and when Brad was by himself,
you stabbed him to death.
- No.
- Then you stashed the knife
in the alley behind
Chuck's house
- so he'd look like the real killer.
- That isn't true.
- No?
- No.
Then answer me this:
How did your cummerbund,
the one you spilled red wine
on... Hold that... It's pretty easy.
See the stain right there?
How did your cummerbund
wind up on Brad's body?
- That isn't mine.
- Of course it is.
The stain in that picture is exactly
the same as the stain in that picture,
and the reason your cummerbund
wound up on Brad's body
is you got blood on it
when you stabbed him.
So you switched them.
And you knew he was
right, he was gonna beat you
at that volunteer
fireman's competition.
Just like he beat you
at football, arm wrestling,
sit-ups and all the others.
It seems preposterous to me
that someone would kill over
something so insignificant.
But you did kill
him, didn't you?
They were just games, Matt.
They didn't matter.
This does.
This is for keeps.
Those whom God
has joined together,
let no one put asunder.
And now that Paul and Laura
have given themselves to each other
through the exchanging of
vows and the exchanging of rings,
I now pronounce
you husband and wife.
All right, everybody, let's go outside
and give them a proper send-off.
Oh, wait, wait, get one of us.
Oh. Ha, ha.
Thanks for everything, especially
for what you did for Chuck.
- Have a good life.
- We will.
- I'll make sure.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Real nice of you to
have the wedding here.
Well, the church was booked,
and I didn't want all those
people from Mt. Harlan
to have to drive all the
way over here again.
Aren't you going
to the reception?
Oh, I may go after a while,
but right now, I'm
gonna do something
that I've wanted to for
the past couple weeks.
Oh, what's that?
- Step outside and I'll show you.
- Oh. Huh.
www.tvsubtitles.net